LUIS RODRÍGUEZ BALTODANO

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+506 83537229

✓ Lrodriguezbaltodano97@gmail.com

Linkedin Profile

<u>Website</u>

PERSONAL SKILLS

Team worker

Great communication

Self-taught

Critical thinking

Conflict Resolution

SKILLS

HTML & CSS

JavaScript / Typescript

Vueis

Reactis

Java

Spring boot

SOL

AEM

SASS

Git

Scrum

SUMMARY

Frontend developer with experience in website development, high experience in Javascript as well as knowledge in frameworks like Vuejs and Reactjs. Ability to learn new tools, be self-taught and teamwork. Also backend experience with Java, Springboot and SQL. Always motivated to learn new ways to create simple and clean code.

EDUCATION

Bacherlor of Computer Science, Present, Universidad Nacional de Costa Rica

FEB 2018 - NOV 2021

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Intern, Accenture

AUG 2021 - NOV 2021

Develop features, meet requirements, maintain existing code and work with responsive components.

Technologies: Angular, Typescript, Java (Spring Boot)

Frontend Developer, Accenture

DEC 2021 - PRESENT

As a frontend developer, meet requirements, write maintainable code, refactor code and create responsive and reusable components.

Technologies: Vuejs, Vuex, SASS, Java, AEM

LANGUAGE

Spanish

Intermediate English